## **TEFANNY I. YOUNG**

(+64) 0226911007 | Tefannyoung@gmail.com
GitHub: TefannYoung
LinkedIn: Tefanny Imanil-Young
Queenstown, New Zealand

## **CAREER OBJECTIVE:**

Experienced hospitality professional with a passion for problem-solving and attention to detail. I am excited to embark on a new career change and move to junior web development role where I can apply my creative and technical skills to build clean, efficient, and user-friendly web applications. I am excited to learn new technologies and collaborate with a team to create innovative solutions that exceed client expectation.

#### **EDUCATION:**

ISTQB Certified Tester Foundation Level (CTFL) | Currently studying

Agile Project Management Foundation | Currently studying

ABC Scrum Master | Currently studying

**Code+, Full-Stack Developer Collection** | Skillsoft Completed 2023

**Graduate Diploma in Tourism & Hospitality Management** | Queenstown Resort College Completed 2019

Bachelor of Science International Hospitality Management Specialize Cruise Line operation in Hotel services | Lyceum of the Philippine University Completed 2014

### **CORE SKILLS:**

00112 01112201					
Frontend	Backend	Framework	Source control	UI / UX	
HTML	JavaScript	Bootstrap	GitHub	Webflow	
CSS	Python	Django		Figma	

## **PROJECTS:**

Project title: Wedding website

**Brief description:** I created a wedding website as a one-stop information guide for the guest.

Frameworks and languages used: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap

GitHub link: <a href="https://github.com/TefannYoung/TheYoungsWedding">https://github.com/TefannYoung/TheYoungsWedding</a>

Project title: My website portfolio

**Brief description:** My portfolio with attached document like my cv, certifications and projects.

Frameworks and languages used: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript GitHub link: <a href="https://github.com/TefannYoung/My-Website-Portfolio">https://github.com/TefannYoung/My-Website-Portfolio</a>

**Project title:** Countries and their Capitals

**Brief description**: I created a quiz game about Countries and Capitals.

Frameworks and languages used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript

**GitHub link:** https://github.com/TefannYoung/Countries-and-their-Capitals

Project title: Portfolio Website

**Brief description:** I make my website portfolio mainly as my practice.

Frameworks and languages used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript GitHub link: <a href="https://github.com/TefannYoung/Trueself">https://github.com/TefannYoung/Trueself</a>

### **Employment History:**

# Woolworths Group | Part-Time | September 2022 – Currently Retail Assistant

### Queenstown, New Zealand

- Providing exceptional customer service
- Greeting customers/welcoming customers
- Assisting customers/serving customers in a timely manner
- Maintaining a clean shop floor
- Standing for long periods

# The Rees Hotel, Luxury Apartments & Lakeside Residences | November 2018 - August 2022 Housekeeping/Self-Checker/Public Area Attendant

### Queenstown, New Zealand

- Inspect rooms before they are available for sale
- Cleans occupied and vacant rooms
- Communicates the status of guestrooms to the Front Office Department
- Cleans and presses the proper's linens, towel and guest clothing
- Maintain soiled and clean inventory items
- Cleans the public area making sure it is neat and tidy
- Doing turndown service at night

### Career Break | June 2016 - October 2018

During this period, I took a career break to take care of my family and while doing that I also pursued full-time study in housekeeping services and IELTS. I am proud of my dedication to my family and commitment to my education, which has helped me acquire a deeper understanding of the hospitality industry and further develop my skills and abilities.

# Infinity Tower Suite | August 2015-September 2015 Housekeeping

## Makati, Philippines

- Inspect rooms before they are available for sale
- Cleans occupied and vacant rooms
- Maintain soiled and clean inventory items

# Bolton Hotel | August 2013-January 2014 Housekeeping

### Wellington, New Zealand

- Wiped, dusted and polished furniture.
- Vacuumed carpets and deep clean stains.
- Change lines and restocked room supplies
- Washed windows and doors and inspected rooms
- Clean bathrooms, made beds, and removed trash